ccasian.com 2017-12-01

# Privacy Policy

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> .

**Information We Collect**

**When you create an account and use our Service, we collect the following types of information from you:**

  * Name;
  * Contact information such as your email address;
  * Demographics information such as what country you are in; what your language preferences are; your age and gender;
  * Payment data such as credit card information and PayPal account information ; and
  * Any other information, such as profile picture, videos, content, and bio, you provide us.

If you create an Account using, or otherwise connect your Account to, your Facebook account, we will also collect information provided to us by Facebook including for example your: name; email address; birthday; geographic location; interests; profile picture; gender; networks; user ID; list of friends; and any information you have made public on your Facebook account.

We automatically collect information about how you use our services, for example, pages you have viewed, the television shows, movies, music videos or other content that you view or favorite, subtitles or segments of content that you edit, genres you prefer, and searches you make. We also collect certain technical information about your device including your Internet protocol address, geo-location information (city and country), your browser type, language and identifying information, your operating system and application version, device types, device model and manufacturer, device identifiers, and your device operating system type and version.

We also use cookies, Web beacons, and URL information to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and the information for which you searched and which you viewed. Cookies are small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer's hard drive while you are viewing a website. We may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent cookies (which usually stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on our Site. Web beacons are digital images that are used to log information on the Services or in our emails. We use Web beacons to manage cookies, count visits, and to learn what marketing works and what does not. We also use Web beacons to tell if you open or act on our emails.

Others, including third party analytics service providers and advertising partners may also collect personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across different Web sites when you use our Services, including as described in this Privacy Policy. This Policy does not apply to and we are not responsible for those other parties.

Third party analytics services may use cookies and web beacons through our Site (for example Google Analytics for Display Advertisers) and platform device identifiers and software agents on and through our mobile Services (for example Flurry) to provide us with information about how you use and interact with our Site.

We use local shared objects, also known as "Flash cookies," to store your preferences or to display content based upon what you view on our websites to personalize your visit. Third parties may also provide certain features on our websites, collect information about your Web browsing activities, and display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity using Flash cookies to collect and store information. Flash cookies are different from other cookies because of the amount of, type of, and way in which data is stored. To learn about privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies click here: <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118> (or in the EU <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/>).

### Sharing Of Your Information

The CCAsian Services may allow you to connect and share your actions, comments, content, profile, and information publicly or with other people. You may control some of the categories of personal information shared via your profile from the account settings menu on the Site. Please be mindful of your own privacy needs as you choose who to connect with and what to share and make public. We cannot control the privacy or security of information you choose to make public or share with others.

By connecting your account to Facebook, you are instructing CCAsian to share your viewing history (information about videos you have viewed) with Facebook, and other users of Facebook and the CCAsian Services, and you expressly give CCAsian permission to disclose and share your viewing history. If you do not want your viewing history to be shared via Facebook, you should not connect your account to Facebook. You can turn off sharing by disconnecting your account from Facebook. We are not responsible for the use or re-sharing by others of any of your viewing history once it is made public. If you do not want your viewing history to be made public, you should not use the CCAsian Services and/or you should adjust your Facebook privacy settings accordingly. We are not responsible for and we do not control Facebook's privacy practices. Please review Facebook's privacy policy for information about how they use your information.

We offer social features to enhance your experience with the CCAsian Services. These features may change from time to time and may vary by device, including the exact manner and extent of information shared as well as the choices available to manage these features. If you choose to participate in the CCAsian Services’ social features, you are consenting to share your viewing history and other activity with other CCAsian users. Within the CCAsian Services, we provide controls over sharing your CCAsian activity. You can prevent sharing your viewing history and other activity with other CCAsian users by adjusting your privacy settings on the CCAsian Site.

### How CCAsian Uses Your Information

**CCAsian generally uses your information to:**

  * Facilitate the creation of and secure your account on our network;
  * Identify you as a user in our system;
  * Provide, personalize, and improve the Services;
  * Communicate with you about your use of the Services;
  * Develop new products and services,
  * Customize the advertising you view and recommend content;
  * Fulfill your requests;
  * Identify the comments you post;
  * Send newsletters, surveys, offers and promotional materials related to the Services and for other marketing purposes of CCAsian;
  * Protect, investigate, and prevent potentially fraudulent, unauthorized, or illegal activities;
  * Protect our rights and the rights of other users; and
  * As otherwise described in this Privacy Policy or in notices we provided to you.

We use your payment information to charge you for paid content or memberships and subscriptions that you request. We may also use your information to verify your geographic location. We may use your geographic location data (city and country) to personalize our Service, to recommend content, determine whether the content you have requested is available in your location. We also aggregate and anonymize all information we collect. We may use or share your aggregated and anonymized data for any purposes allowed by applicable law.

### How CCAsian Discloses Your Information

We may share your information as follows:

  * We may share your personal information with your consent or at your direction.
  * We may also share your information with others who perform services on our behalf.
  * We may disclose your information if we believe we are required to do so by law, or to comply with a court order, judicial or other government subpoena, or warrant.
  * We also may disclose your information if we believe doing so is appropriate or necessary to prevent any liability, or fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses or to protect CCAsian and our Services; or any rights, property, or personal safety of CCAsian or others.
  * In the event that CCAsianis acquired by or merged with another company or involved in any other business deal (or negotiation of a business deal) involving sale or transfer of all or part of our business or assets, we may transfer or assign your information as part of the transaction. Finally, in the event of insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership, information may be transferred as a business asset.

We may also share aggregated and anonymized data with our partners, advertisers and other third parties. For example, we may tell studios how many times a particular episode of a television series was watched and by which demographics.

### Third Party Advertisers

We permit advertisements to be delivered to you by third party Internet advertising companies (also called ad networks or network advertisers). These companies may use cookies, Web beacons, platform device identifiers, software agents, and other technologies to collect non-personally identifiable information about your visits over time on our Service and across other websites to deliver advertisements to you targeted to your interests, measure their effectiveness and personalize advertising content, and to understand the usage and visitation of the Services and the other applications and websites tracked by these advertising companies. We do not have access to or control over cookies, Web beacons, platform device identifiers, software agents, or other technologies that they may use. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of third party advertisers. You should check the privacy policy of the third party advertiser to determine how it handles information it separately collects from you. In addition, the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) offers information about some of the Internet advertising companies we may use. To learn about interest based advertising by Tremor visit [Tremor's privacy policy](http://tremorvideo.com/about-us/privacy/). To learn about Apple's interest based advertising visit [Apple's privacy policy](http://www.apple.com/privacy/).

### Security

CCAsian takes commercially reasonable steps to help protect your Information against loss, misuse and unauthorized access, or disclosure. No company can fully prevent security risks, however. To help protect yourself and your information, choose a unique password for our Services and do not use a password on our Services that you would use on any other website or online service.

### Dispute Resolution

If you believe that CCAsian has not adhered to this Statement, please contact CCAsian by e-mail at. We will do our best to address your concerns. If you feel that your complaint has been addressed incompletely, we invite you to let us know for further investigation. If you and CCAsian are unable to reach a resolution to the dispute, you and CCAsian will settle the dispute exclusively under the rules of the American Arbitration Association ([http://www.adr.org](http://www.adr.org/)).

### Information Choices

You may opt out of receiving promotional emails from CCAsian by following the instructions in those emails. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as emails about your accounts or our ongoing business relations. You may also send requests about your personal information, including changes to your contact preferences, changes to or deletions of your information or content you post, and requests to opt-out of sharing your personal information with third parties by emailing Please note that deletion of your information or content does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information posted on the Services.

CCAsian gives you certain choices about how we collect personally identifiable information as described in this Policy. But we may not recognize or respond to your Web browser's "do not track" signal and other mechanisms that provide consumers the ability to exercise choice regarding the collection of personally identifiable information about an individual consumer’s online activities over time and across third-party Web sites or online services. Most Web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services of our Site including certain opt-out cookies. Cookie management tools provided by your browser usually will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies click here: <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118> (or in the EU <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/>).

We encourage you to review the privacy policies of our third party advertisers to learn about your choices about information they collect from you. In addition, the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) offers information about some of the Internet advertising companies we may use, including how to opt-out of interest based advertising they deliver. To opt-out of interest based advertising by Tremor visit [Tremor's privacy policy](http://tremorvideo.com/about-us/privacy/). To learn how to opt-out of interest based advertising by Apple visit the [iAd support page](http://support.apple.com/kb/HT4228). To learn how to opt out of Flurry Analytics mobile tracking and personalized ads/recommendations from Flurry visit [Flurry's privacy policy](http://www.flurry.com/privacy-policy.html). To opt-out of Google Analytics web tracking you can download [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

### Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy

From time to time, we may revise the Privacy Policy. To help you stay current of any changes, we note the date the Privacy Policy was last updated above.

### CCAsian Contact Information

Please contact CCAsian with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, your Information, our third-party disclosure practices, or your consent choices via . You can also request access to or that we correct or delete your personal information at any time by emailing.
